<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title/><link>http://example.org/</link><description>Recent content on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 17:53:03 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Closures</title><link>http://example.org/posts/closures/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 17:53:03 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/closures/</guid><description>When writing functions that expect functions as arguments
func calculator(numberA: Int, numberB: Int, operation: (Int, Int) -&amp;gt; Int) -&amp;gt; Int { return operation(numberA, numberB) } rather than writing the expected argument as an explicit named function
func addOperation(nA: Int, nB: Int) -&amp;gt; Int { return nA + nB } and calling it like
calculator(numberA: 8, numberB: 3, operation: addOperation) we can pass it as a closure instead
calculator(numberA: 8, numberB: 3, operation: { (nA: Int, nB: Int) -&amp;gt; Int in return nA + nB }) which can be simplified in a number of ways.</description></item><item><title>Getting Up and Running</title><link>http://example.org/posts/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 17:34:56 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/getting-started/</guid><description>This site was made using Hugo, which has lowered the barrier to entry for me running my own blog.
Every time I want to create a new post, I can just run
hugo new some-new-post.md from the root directory of this repo.
For a local server instance I run
hugo server -D where the -D flag sets drafts to true, meaning I can view any posts that are still marked as drafts.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://example.org/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/about/</guid><description>Consultant
I like helping people solve problems. I&amp;rsquo;m currently working as a consultant based in the UK, with a focus on mobile engineering.
Mobile Engineer
I have experience with native app development for both Android (Kotlin) and iOS (Swift). My work has exposed me to both traditional approaches to UI development (xml layouts in Android, UIKit for iOS), and modern approaches (Jetpack Compose, SwiftUI).
More recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working with tools such as Firebase to leverage data-driven approach to feature development, combining Analytics, Remote Config, Audiences and A/B testing to understand which features are most valuable to users.</description></item></channel></rss>